Oh! Five more minutes.
(Leonard:)That's what you said five minutes ago.
(Leonard:)Amy and Penny are already in the car,
move it.
(Sheldon:)How come I never get to do
anything I wanna do?
(Howard:)If he really wants to stay and finish,
I can give him a ride home.
(Sheldon:)Please, Leonard. He said it's okay.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, it's...
Wait, I can go home without you? Bye.
(Sheldon:)Howard, I have a few questions.
(Sheldon:)I found three bowling pins.
(Sheldon:)Now, do you juggle these
or are you missing seven?
(Sheldon:)- Juggle.
- You health nuts kill me.
Oh, my God, it's beautiful!
And look,
you found the juggling pins I hid.
Now, a couple more items.
(Sheldon:)Howard, I found this letter
from your dad in a box.
- Based on content, it could either be filed...
- Wait, you opened this?
I had to find out if it's
personal correspondence or memorabilia.